suck
on to cnbc tv 18 exclusive party
enterprises may exit from icici lombard
general insurance we learn from sources
the conglomerate must sell its entire
stake wire block teal next week yash
joins us now with more yash what are you
picking up well that's correct sharing
it's a it's a large transaction in the
general insurance space what we've been
given to understand from our sources is
that bharti enterprise
is looking to sell its entire stake when
it comes to icici lombard general
insurance uh this could happen through a
block deal and what we're going to
understand from our bankers is that this
could happen as early as the first half
of next week itself as far as the stake
itself is concerned bharti enterprises
they own about 3.72 percent stake in
icsc lombard at the current market price
this transaction could be nearly 2200
crore rupees uh now uh how does really
uh bharti enterprise have stake in ics
at lombard this is because after the
merger of bharti axa general insurance
and icici lombard bharti enterprise and
axa they both got nearly four percent
stake in icsc lombard axa exercised this
particular option and sold its entire
stake last year through a block deal and
now we've been given to understand that
bharti enterprise could exercise the
same option we've written to all parties
involved in this particular transaction
and bharti enterprises has replied
saying that do not comment on market
speculations we are still waiting for a
reply from icici
yash mani thanks for joining us a quick
check of some of the other headlines
eureka forbes has opened strong on its
first day of trading the stock opened
its account at 495 rupees a share much
higher than the 210 rupees private
equity firm advent international is
offering as its opened up for price for
a 26 stake in the company the stock
closing at 470 rupees and 25 peso per
share this was also the day's low for
the stock as it triggered the five
percent lower circuit food delivery app
zomatos shares hit a fresh low today
slipping 5.5 the day after the company
announced a merger with online grocery
platform blinkit analysts say investors
are becoming very of the company as it
continues to spend despite its
deteriorating financials the supreme
court has refused to pass an interim
order on relief sought by amazon to
protect future retail assets but has
agreed to hear amazon's plea next week
ashby joins us now with more ashby take
us to what transpired today
well amazon for long has been arguing
that there needs to be an order for
protecting uh the assets of future
retail and that's the same application
in fact they moved today as well uh the
grouse that future expressed was that
this is a last minute filing future
pointed out that the 370 page
application was filed just five minutes
prior to the hearing in the apex court
uh however amazon stuck to its guns
pointed out that there needs to be a
protective order uh they pointed out
that there is no rationale for moving
the arbitral tribunal once again because
the arbitral tribunal has already
granted interim orders interim
protective orders in the form of the
emergency arbitrator order and if that
is not being respected if that is being
violated what is the point of seeking
additional orders from the same arbitral
tribunal now future again stuck to it
guns pointed out that the substance of
this entire proceeding before the apex
court was limited to resumption of the
arbitration and given the fact that both
the sites future as well as amazon are
welcoming the idea of resumption of
arbitration uh there is no longer need
of proceedings here uh before the apex
court but nonetheless amazon given the
position that they've taken the apec
squad for now has not passed any owners
but nonetheless has agreed next week uh
to take up amazon's application and to
consider that question of whether or not
to grant any protective orders with
respect to retail assets of future
retail ash but penny thanks for joining
us now the organized furniture market in
india is here